Eric Stevens

Computer Science student and creative with strong knowledge and experience in managing e-commerce, marketing, and creating successful projects. Very motivated to learn as much as possible in tech-related jobs, and specifically to understand what types of problems tech consumers are experiencing in 2020--and to apply that understanding into problem solving and creating potential future solutions or improvements.

Brooklyn, NY
(646) 856-3975
ericbstevens92@gmail.com
www.outlaw2o2o.com

EXPERIENCE

OUTLAW NYC — Event Series

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

- Created an event series showcasing underground electronic music/production
- Built a strong network of NYC based artists
- Design and maintain the website, run marketing analytics and campaigns, handle all sales and finances / budgets, release mixes and original tracks, as well as oversee all creative and operational aspects of the project
- Oversaw the event becoming a word of mouth sensation and grassroots community project

Melting Point NYC — Fundraiser / Political Action / Event Series

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2019

- Co-founded an event series which aimed to raise urgent funds for a legal nonprofit aiding migrants, asylum seekers, and deportees at the Tijuana / Los Angeles border (called Al Otro Lado), while also cultivating the underground music scene in NYC
- Raised over \$20K for Al Otro Lado in just a year, and had over 4,000 people attend our NYE 2019 event

Parke and Ronen, Garment District, NY — Project Manager / E-commerce

FEBRUARY 2017 - JUNE 2018

- Designed and launched a new click and mortar store for NYC menswear designers, Parke and Ronen
- Maintained a wide variety of aspects of the online platform
- Obtained a very diverse array of knowledge revolving around e-commerce

EDUCATION

Brooklyn College CUNY, Brooklyn, NY — Computer Science (BS) / Minor in Cognitive Science

AUGUST 2019 - FALL 2021

Austin Community College, Austin, TX — *Psychology (AAS)*

SKILLS

Customer Service

Web development

Programming

Graphic Design (35mm film photography / Adobe Lightroom / Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Illustrator)

Music Production / Sound Design (Ableton)

Microsoft Excel

MARKETING SKILLS

E-commerce Mgmt.

Quickbooks Inventory Mgmt.

Lightspeed POS / Inventory

CMS

Shopify, Wix, WordPress

SMS and Email Marketing Campaigns

Analytics / Online Merchandising

Sales Reports (Excel)

August 2012 - May 2014